const questions = [{
    "qIndex":"0",
    "question":"8*9",
    "ans1":"60",
    "ans2":"70",
    "ans3":"74",
    "correctAns":"72",
    "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"1",
     "question":"2*7",
     "ans1":"18",
     "ans2":"10",
     "ans3":"16",
     "correctAns":"14",
     "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"2",
    "question":"3*4",
    "ans1":"32",
    "ans2":"20",
    "ans3":"10",
    "correctAns":"12",
    "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"3",
     "question":"4*6",
     "ans1":"18",
     "ans2":"25",
     "ans3":"20",
     "correctAns":"24",
     "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"4",
    "question":"1*5",
    "ans1":"6",
    "ans2":"4",
    "ans3":"0",
    "correctAns":"5",
    "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"5",
     "question":"9*9",
     "ans1":"100",
     "ans2":"70",
     "ans3":"80",
     "correctAns":"81",
     "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"6",
    "question":"3*8",
    "ans1":"27",
    "ans2":"21",
    "ans3":"16",
    "correctAns":"24",
    "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"7",
     "question":"4*5",
     "ans1":"10",
     "ans2":"30",
     "ans3":"25",
     "correctAns":"20",
     "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"8",
    "question":"6*7",
    "ans1":"15",
    "ans2":"36",
    "ans3":"44",
    "correctAns":"42",
    "scores":"10"
 },
 {
    "qIndex":"9",
    "question":"4*7",
    "ans1":"28",
    "ans2":"12",
    "ans3":"42",
    "correctAns":"24",
    "scores":"10"
 }
 ]
export default questions;